# MONA ASHMAWY

- @ mo.ashmawey@gmail.com
- h 01001622725
- a Shebin El Kom, El-menofia 51132

be.net/MonaAshmawey

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, JQuery, PHP and JavaScript. Experience building products for desktop, phone and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to customer's services. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

## **EDUCATION**

Faculty of Science Menofia Governorate • 06/2014

Bachelor of Science: Mathematics A nd Computer Science

#### SKILLS

- Web user interfaces
- · Design patterns and principles
- · Business analysis
- · Planning and scheduling
- Conflict resolution
- Public relations
- Coding
- UX Research

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe indesign
- · Adobe after effect
- Sketch
- Html5
- Css3
- Sass
- Jquery
- Wordpress

### WORK HISTORY

Children's Cancer Hospital Egypt 57357 - Sr. UX/UX Designer Cairo, Cairo • 04/2015 - Current

- Developed, coded and updated medical and fundraising sites for clients such as 57357, AFNCI, ECN USA and ECN CA
- Spearhead production of page content such as visuals and text copy to meet project specifications
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement
- Took concepts and produced design mockups and prototypes to strengthen designs, enhance user experiences and improve site interactions
- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects

Pear Academy - Web Design Instructor Shebin El-kom , Menofia • 09/2014 - 04/2015

- Worked with web design to devise and implement support plans to help students excel
- Reviewed class and student records to look for areas in need of improvement and implement plans of action

Pearogram - Web and Graphic Designer Shebin El kom, Menofia • 03/2014 - 10/2014

- Created and implemented web design to communicate mission, values and beliefs of community
- Developed site navigation by categorizing content and funneling traffic through content

Pear Academy - Graphic Designer Shebin El kom, Menofia • 11/2013 - 03/2014

 Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones